EL MOUMEN YASSINE



HRIS/IT PROJECT MANAGER

CONTACT

ADRESSE

MOBILE : +212-669-836412

EMAIL : elmoumenyassine@outlook.com

LINKEDIN : linkedin.com/in/elmoumenyassine

: Gueliz | Marrakech | Maroc

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

CONSULTANT AND BUSINESS ADVISOR

AINSI CO, GBC, WEBFLUT 2022 - 2023
Consulting in strategy, sourcing and subcontracting

IT PROJECT MANAGER CRM. ELEARNING & BPO

GBC, SOPLAST, MTO, HL, MTO 2022
Private Events, SMM, Internal Solutions, Funnels

TRAINING QUALITY PROJECT MANAGER

GE : Centres de Formation 2021 - 2022 89 Training engineering, materials included

TRAINER, REFERENT, EXPERT BUSINESS & TOOLS

Club Med FBS | Webhelp 2018 - 2021

Supervisor training and sales solutions

EDUCATION

CEGOS | INTRA TRAINING 2021

Trainers, succeed in your training Webhelp University

BACCALAURÉAT PHYSICS CHEMISTRY 2018

Physics Chemistry Department | Good Mention Imam Malik High School

PROFILE

As an experienced IT project manager with more than 5 years in the field, I am a natural leader able to lead a team to deliver innovative and efficient solutions in response to the needs of our customers. With a good understanding of software development processes, Agile methodologies and current technological issues, I am motivated to take on the most complex challenges for our clients.

CONTRIBUTIONS

MANAGEMENT OF DEV AND ADMINISTRATION PROJECTS

FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT AND DESIGN

COPYWRITING, DOCUMENTATION, ENGINEERING

SKILLS

High-Ticket
Sales

Marketing
Omnichannel
SaaS

Analyse

High-Ticket
Sales

Design
Thinking

WRITTEN SPOKEN LANGUAGES

French English

NOTABLE TOOLS

